{
    "id": "33884800ca454825b94a7940ba42f29b",
    "title": "Identify The Adverb",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is so pigheaded you can’t reason with him.",
            "description": "Here so modifies the adjective pigheaded. Only an adverb can modify an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "pigheaded",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "70698b55a29f40669a7233f88eeccda8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sailing alone around the world was quite a pilgrimage.",
            "description": "Quite is an adverb indicating degree. It shows to what extent.",
            "answers": [
                "sailing",
                "quite",
                "privilege"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "478836f8015140b19a444196a2cbe6c8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The admiral was always nonchalant in the face of danger.",
            "description": "Always is an adverb of time. It answers the question when.",
            "answers": [
                "always",
                "nonchalant",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "73b1ec76513042cc88c84feb0f79143e"
        },
        {
            "question": "A person’s outward appearance was formerly thought to reveal his character.",
            "description": "Formerly is an adverb of time. Most words ending in ly are adverbs.",
            "answers": [
                "outward",
                "formerly",
                "reveal"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "10a4cf63fd42403ca7a56d190030fb7c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Wearing nothing but blue clothing is only one of her peculiarities.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "nothing",
                "blue",
                "only"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c8477714b7cc4ace91327409f35950ad"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was seen driving northward.",
            "description": "Words indicating place are adverbs.",
            "answers": [
                "seen",
                "driving",
                "northward"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c9820a77580e4f79a163413e0d6b1161"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have told you this twice.",
            "description": "Twice is an adverb of frequency. It answers the question how often.",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "this",
                "twice"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "91bc983c4c6b426cbc9cde69658e9f9f"
        },
        {
            "question": "That day he arrived late.",
            "description": "Here late modifies the verb arrived. Hence it is an adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "arrived",
                "late"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e68fe5dd29b1432e9c51c17358bd3fd5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have already spoken to him about this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "already",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cee789de36b2449b911041ec4c162359"
        },
        {
            "question": "Luckily we escaped unhurt.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "luckily",
                "escaped",
                "unhurt"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f3767c08a07d4bcea20e23dfcd1313a9"
        },
        {
            "question": "My dog understands everything. He is almost human.",
            "description": "Here the adverb almost modifies the adjective human. ",
            "answers": [
                "everything",
                "almost",
                "human"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "162ff8d0e17049b3b9b51e1389a6bbe3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am fully prepared for the examination.",
            "description": "Here the adverb fully modifies the adjective prepared. ",
            "answers": [
                "am",
                "fully",
                "prepared"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3e08a06f8e97410da80d0f22bf17258e"
        }
    ]
}